Brand
02
CANDORLOV is a medical grade skincare brand from
BIOBIJOUs expertise in fillers and skin boosters.
Inspired by real clinical insights, we create skincare solutions that bring professional
results into your daily routine by blending science with beauty.
2024 2025
: Revenue 4.7 billion KRW
Apr 2024 May 2024 Nov 2024 Dec 2024 Jan 2025 June 2025
Brand launch : Available on Expanded Skincare Debut on Tmall Launched in USA via Introduced 7 skincare
Released 4 Xiaohongshu, Line : Released 5 Amazon and TikTok products : Now offered
skincare products Douyin, and Kuaishou additional products on NS Homeshopping
Brand concept
03
CANDORLOV offers more than just beautydelivers true skin science.
We focus not only on whats visible on the surface, but also the subtle changes happening beneath the skin.
We prioritize the right ingredients, concentrations, and skin types to deliver the best results.
Functional Care
Hypoallergenic
Formula Routine
Low-irritation formulas that
Targeted solutions with High-performance
are safe for sensitive skin
the right functional formulas skincares for everyday use
Strategic direction
04
BRAND DIRECTION
CANDORLOV is a medical grade skincare brand built on lab technology and a deep archive
of beauty science, designed to care for specific skin concerns with precision.
Target Customers 01 Product Position 02
Targeting late 20s to Early 50s Gentle but high-performance skincare
 
Users seeking single-focused functional skincare Hypoallergenic medical skincare safe for post-procedure use
 
Users valuing ingredients and visible changes High-performance formulas focused on ingredient, texture, and efficacy
 
Users needing professional care Daily-use routines designed for both clinical use and home care
Brand Identity 03 Brand Strength 04
Tailored skincare solutions inspired by clinical treatment insights
Advanced brand infused with specialized dermatological data
 
High-performance skincare inspired by our beauty expertise Formulated with deep understanding of dermatological procedures
 
Advanced solutions powered by technologies developed closest to the skin Structurally flexible to adapt across both clinical and retail settings
 
From skin science to professional home care Skincare lineup with targeted formulas to care specific skin concerns
Recommended by professionals
05
MEDICAL SPECIALIST
From Clinics to Daily Skincare Routines :
CANDORLOV CANDORLOV offers personalized skincare solutions designed for structured,
multi-channel usefrom clinics to retail.
Displayed Clinics-Top in Seoul
O.N Clinic, The Up Plastic surgery Clinic, U&Lin Plastic surgery
Clinic, OLLE Plastic surgery Clinic
Displayed Products
Our recovery and soothing lines-
CANDORLOV is trusted by professionals
Relaxing mist, Collagen boosting glass cream, etc.
and users, becoming an essential part of
post-procedure recovery routines.
Displayed Area
Front desk, Treatment rooms, and Consultation rooms.
Touchpoints at Clinics
Used and recommended by clinics as part of post-treatment care.
Marketing
06
DEBUT IN TV HOMESHOPPING
IN JUNE 2025
Sold
Sold-out
64,000
Record
Sheets
Marketing
07
SNS
@candorlov_us @candorlov_official @candorlov.official
Marketing
08
GLOBAL SHOPPING LIVE
USD 2.4 MILLION
2025 Shopping Live Sales :
Marketing
09
GLOBAL PRODUCT REVIEW
SJ
Vicki Maddeen
5 stars! Love this mask!
Hands down the best mask Ive used. Pair it with the Candorlov Collagen Boosting
Ive been using this mask for a week, and my skin already feels firmer and looks lifted.
Glass Cream..... sister, get ready! Cause its good stuff! Your skin will shine!
My wrinkles are looking better, and my skin feels super hydrated. The Collagen Water and
I have 52 year old skin and it looks better after using these for 6 months than it has
Pomegranate Exosome are really helping with elasticity. So, the mask has 840,000 PPM
in a very long time. Go! Go ahead and buy it!
of collagen. Honestly, I had no idea what PPM meant, so I Googled it. Turns out, PPM means
parts per million, so thats 840,000 parts of collagen for every million parts of the formula.
Katherine Zinkovich
Tamara_Empowerment4Life
Lather it on dry skin; it bubbles as you lather & feels clean and not dry
Fabulous I received it yesterday and I got it in a quick amount of time.
This was a pleasant, new experience. The gel dispensed is normal and unassuming,
The packaging is beautiful, easy to apply. It comes with its own applicator.
but when you apply it to your dry skin and massage it in, it lathers up and bubbles.
Extremely easy to apply and to peel off and it makes your skin especially
As you lather, it feels more like a luxurious lotion than a soap. You can leave it
if you have mature skin. At 57 years old. I love it!
on a minute or two before rinsing off.
Summer
OnePickyMom
Best Collagen Boost for My Skin!
I really like this Candorlov Ceramide Serum with Glutathione Dragon Blood. I apply it after
Ive tried a lot of collagen products, but this one is on another level! Its packed with
cleansing and toner, before moisturizer. The little beads are a fun addition and seem to burst
7 types of collagen, and I could really feel the difference after just one use. My skin felt
when rubbed or patted into your skin. This serum absorbs instantly for me, and leaves
so much smoother, more elastic, and definitely looked more radiant. The instant glass skin
my skin noticeably softer and smoother.
effect is no joke  my face had that beautiful, healthy glow! What I love most is how gentle
it is on my sensitive skin  no irritation at all, which is rare for me.
Marketing
10
INSTAGRAM
Marketing
11
TIKTOK
Marketing
12
WANGHONG

Prodcut
13
ORIGINAL LINE
RELAXING MIST ONLINE SERUM
50ML / 48,000 won 30ML / 48,000 won
A Serum with Ceramide Capsules for
Soothing, Hydrating & Revitalizing Oil Serum Mist Strengthening Skin Barrier
ONLINE CREAM RELAX SHEET MASK
30ML / 48,000 won 25ML * 5EA / 32,000 won
A Recovery Cream for Irritated Skin
and Boosts Self-generation Power Intensive Soothing & Hydrating Sheet Mask
RED PORE CLEAN CLAY MUD PACK COMPACT BUBBLE SPARKLE MASK
80ML / 34,900 won 100G / 46,500 won
Innovative Bubble Mask that Flushes Out
A Creamy Mud Pack that Deeply Cleanses Pores
Sebum Deep in Pores
and Sebum to Reduce Puffiness
GLOW LIFTING MASK COLLAGEN BOOSTING GLASS CREAM
70ML / 35,900 won 50ML / 35,900 won
72-Hour Glow Cream with a High-Refractive
Glossy Formula
15-minute Secret to Glassy, Smooth Skin: Peel-off Mask
LOW MOLECULAR COLLAGEN
LIFTING MASK 30G * 5EA / 42,000 won
84% High-concentrated 200DA
Collagen Hydrogel Lifting Mask
Prodcut
14
NEW PRODUCTS
DEWY PDRN YOGA-PAD DEWY PDRN YOGA-PAD (REFILL)
160ML * 60PADS / 28,000 won 160ML * 60PADS / 23,000 won
-2025
Cooling Fit & Firming Pads for Instant Elasticity Cooling Fit & Firming Pads for Instant Elasticity
ICY PUFF SHEET MASK ICY SPOTLIGHT SHEET MASK
25ML * 10EA / 35,000 won 25ML * 10EA / 45,000 won

A Sheet Mask Cools Skin By -11 C to Cooling Sheet Mask for Summer Recovery,
Calm Redness and Puffiness Melasma Treatment
GOLDEN DROP OIL SERUM BLOOMING COOL SHOT
30ML / 43,000 won AMPOULE 2000
30ML / 43,000 won
Calming & Repairing Ampoule with
Bursting with Vitamin Nutrition 
Cooling-Coated Spicules
Antioxidant Serum for Radiant Skin
FIRMING PEPTIDE SERUM SILK TANGLE CREAM
35ML / 45,000 won 50ML / 42,000 won
Elastic Thread Cream that Rebuilds
the Skins Structure.
Thread-Like Lifting Serum for Firmer, Fuller Skin
Product : CANDORLOV ONLINE CREAM
15
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV Oline Cream
Amount 30mL Price 48,000 won
Keypoint
Soothing, Repairing, Boosting Self-generation
Summary
Formulated to improve and restore various skin concerns such as
damage, dryness, wrinkles, redness, and more. This cream helps
maintain healthy skin while supporting recovery and regeneration.
Clinical Test
Skin Elasticity Improvement Skin barrier Improvement Skin Redness Relief
Irritated Skin Relief Skin Self-renewal Improvement Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
03
Centella Asiatica
01
Dragons Blood
04
Licorice Root
02 05
Matrixyl Green Tea
Product : CANDORLOV RELAXING MIST
16
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV Relaxing Mist
Amount 50mL Price 48,000 won
Keypoint
Hydrating, Soothing, Improving Skin Barrier
Summary
A dual-layer formula combining a skin-repairing ampoule an
a moisturizing toner, delivering intensive care with ease.
Clinical Test
Moisturizing Effect Improvement Skin Barrier Strengthen
Skin Relief Effect Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 02
Dragons Blood Centella Asiatica
03 04
Vitamin B12(Pink Vitamin) 3 Types of Hyaluronic Acid
05 06
Rose of Jericho Panthenol
Product : CANDORLOV ONLINE SERUM
17
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV Online Serum
Amount 30mL Price 48,000 won
Keypoint
Protecting, Hydrating, Smoothing
Summary
Deep absorption, instant hydration, and ceramide barrier
protection while strengthening the skins natural barrier
and keeping it soft and smooth.
Ingredients
01
Dragons Blood
02
Ceramide
03
Glutathione
Product : CANDORLOV RELAX SHEET MASK
18
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV Relax Sheet Mask
Amount 25mL * 5EA Price 32,000 won
Keypoint
Reducing Puffiness, Soothing, Repairing
Summary
Infused with Dragons Blood extract, this mask soothes and
restores damaged skin. The microfiber sheet adheres tightly
to enhance nutrient absorption.
Clinical Test
Puffiness Improvement Cooling Effect Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 02
Dragons Blood Centella Asiatica
03 04
Glyceryl Glucoside Pumpkin Extract
Product : CANDORLOV LOW MOLECULAR COLLAGEN LIFTING MASK
19
NMPA CPNP SCPN
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV Low Molecular Collagen Lifting Mask
Amount 30G * 5EA Price 42,000 won
Keypoint
Lifting, Anti-aging, Glowing
Summary
Contains 840,000 ppm hydrolyzed collagen to lift and improve
skin elasticity. The unique formulation helps firm and strengthen
the skin from within.
Clinical Test
Skin Elasticity Improvement Skin Lifting Effect Skin Cooling Effect
Skin Glowing Improvement Skin Aging Index Improvement
Face Tightening Improvement Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 02
Collagen-mode PHYTOPDRNLOTUS
03 04
Pomegranate Exosome Oligo-HA Solution 1%
PRODUCT : CANDORLOV COLLAGEN BOOSTING GLASS CREAM
20
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV Collagen Boosting Glass Cream
Amount 50mL Price 35,900 won
Keypoint
Hydrating, Firming, Glowing
Summary
Delivers collagen and deep hydration to instantly improve skin
elasticity and brightness. Provides 72-hour long-lasting moisture,
suitable even for sensitive skin.
Clinical Test
Skin Brightening Effect Hydrating Effect for 72 Hours
Skin Elasticity Improvement Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 02
Collagen-mode PHYTOPDRNLOTUS
03 04
Pomegranate Exosome Oligo-HA Solution 1%
PRODUCT : CANDORLOV GLOW LIFTING MASK
21
NMPA CPNP SCPN
Product
CANDORLOV Glow Lifting Mask
Amount 70mL Price 35,900 won
Keypoint
Firming, Glowing, Boosting Radiance
Summary
Formulated with COLLA7VEN  a complex of 7 types of collagen
 to deeply hydrate and improve skin elasticity. The gentle peel-off
texture lifts away easily, leaving skin firm, radiant, and glowing.
Clinical Test
Hydrating Effect for 72 Hours Skin Lifting Effect
Skin Luminous Improvement Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01
COLLA7VEN
02
Flavonoid Exosome
03
Chickweed
PRODUCT : CANDORLOV RED PORE CLEAN CLAY MUD PACK
22
NMPA
Product
CANDORLOV Red Pore Clean Clay Mud Pack
Amount 80mL Price 34,900 won
Keypoint
Reducing Puffiness, Pore Cleansing,
Removing Sebum&Impurity
Summary
Bentonite and Kaolin deeply cleanse and control excess
sebum, soothing and hydrating ingredients visibly vitalize
the skin and tightens pores.
Clinical Test
Pore Cleansing Effect Skin Texture Improvement
Skin Tone Enhancement Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 02
Kaolin Dragons Blood
03 04
Bentonite Gluconolactone
Product : CANDORLOV COMPACT BUBBLE SPARKLE MASK
23
NMPA
Product
CANDORLOV Compact Bubble Sparkle Mask
Amount 100g Price 46,500 won
Keypoint
Pore Refining, Removing Sebum&Impurity,
Skin Tone Clarifying
Summary
Thick, dense foam lifts away dirt and excess oil while helping
to tighten pores. A soothing and moisturizing blend of Dragon Blood,
Panthenol, and Placenta.
Clinical Test
Pore Tightening Effect Skin Texture Improvement
Skin Tone Enhancement Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01
Dragons Blood
02
5 Types of Peptide
03
Phyto Placenta
Product : CANDORLOV ICY PUFF SHEET MASK
24
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV ICY Puff Sheet Mask
Amount Price
25mL * 10EA 35,000 won
Keypoint
Cooling, Hydrating, Soothing, Reducing Puffiness
Summary
Lowers skin temperature by up to -11C. Soothes redness
and UV-stimulated skin while protecting the skin barrier.
Clinical Test
Soothing UV Damaged Skin Relief of Skin Heat
Cooling of Skin Temperature by -11C Reduction of Puffiness
Enhancement Skin Barrier Skin Tightening Skin Lifting
Improvement of Eye Fine Lines Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 Alpine Glacier Water 02 Niacinamide
03 Caffeine Water 04 ICESCREEN
PRODUCT : CANDORLOV ICY SPOTLIGHT SHEET MASK
25
Anti-wrinkle / Brightening
Product
CANDORLOV ICY Spotlight Sheet Mask
Amount Price
25mL * 10EA 45,000 won
Keypoint
Cooling, Soothing, Brightening, Melasma Relief
Summary
Instant -8.7C skin cooling effect. A powerful summer-aging
care mask that helps relieve heat from UV exposure while
targeting wrinkles, loss of elasticity, and pigmentation.
Clinical Test
Relief of Skin Heat Cooling of Skin temperature by -8.7C
Soothing UV Damaged Skin Enhancement Skin Barrier Skin Tightening
Improvement of Eye Fine Lines Skin Lifting Relief of Melasma
Reduction of Puffiness Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 Alpine Glacier Water 02 Niacinamide
03 Caffeine Water 04 ICESCREEN
PRODUCT : CANDORLOV DEWY PDRN YOGA-PAD
26
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV Dewy PDRN Yoga-Pad
Amount Price
160mL / 60 Pads 28,000 won
Keypoint
Soothing, Firming, Hydrating, Exfoliating
Summary
Daily serum pads infused with firming and moisturizing ingredients
to restore elasticity and leave your skin plump and hydrated.
Clinical Test
Relief of Skin Heat Exfoliating Effect Enhancement of Skin Elasticity
Skin Glowing Effect Anti-Wrinkle Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
03 PHA
01 Rose PDRN
04 3 Types of Hyaluronic Acid
02 Multi-Peptide 05 Panthenol
Product : CANDORLOV BLOOMING COOL SHOT AMPOULE 2000
27
Anti-wrinkle / Brightening
Product
CANDORLOV Blooming Cool Shot Ampoule 2000
Amount Price
30mL 43,000 won
Keypoint
Cooling, Soothing, Brightening, Melasma Relief
Summary
Instantly soothes the skin with ice-coated spicules while
improving elasticity and boosting skin volume.
Clinical Test
Cooling Effect Skin Heat Rise Defense Effect Smile Line Improvement
Pore Refining Effect Relief Melasma and Dark Spot Exfoliating Effect
Skin Soothing Effect Aging Index Improvement Improving Eye Fine Lines
Skin Elasticity Improvement Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 Ice Spicules 02 Soothing Cooler
03 Lavender PDRN 04 Amino Acid Complex
Product : CANDORLOV GOLDEN DROP OIL SERUN
28
Anti-wrinkle / Brightening
Product
CANDORLOV Golden Drop Oil Serum
Amount Price
30mL 43,000 won
Keypoint
Repairing, Vitalizing, Improving Skin Turnover
Summary
Vitamin-rich oil beads boost skin vitality and deliver essential
nutrients for a radiant, revitalized complexion.
Clinical Test
Skin Density Improvement Protection of Skin Barrier from Irritation
Skin Elasticity Care Effect Skin Glowing Effect
Improving Skin Turnover Skin Soothing Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 Propolis 02 Sea Buckthorn Oil
03 Tocopheryl Acetate 04 Dermabiotics LRH
Product : CANDORLOV FIRMING PEPTIDE SERUM
29
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDOROV Firming Peptide Serum
Amount Price
35mL 45,000 won
Keypoint
Firming, Anti-aging, Plumping
Summary
Infused with botox-inspired peptides and four patented
ingredients, this silk-thread ampoule enhances elasticity,
volume, and strengthens the skin barrier  all in one.
Clinical Test
Face Lifting Effect Eye Bag Lifting Effect Aging Index Improvement
Skin Tightening Effect Skin Elasticity Enhancement
Improving Skin Density Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 Argireline Amplified peptide 02 Aqualicia Bio
03 Yoguraise 04 Dermabiotics LRH
Product : CANDORLOV SILK TANGLE CREAM
30
NMPA
Anti-wrinkle
Product
CANDORLOV Silk Tangle Cream
Amount Price
50mL 42,000 won
Keypoint
Lifting, Anti-aging, Skin Density Improvement, Firming
Summary
Pink collagen capsules and silky thread-like texture form
a lifting film on the skin, rebuilding collapsed skin structure
and restoring firmness.
Clinical Test
Cheek Volume Restoration Jawline Lifting Effect
Pore Minimization Lower Face Lifting Effect
Deep Moisturization Hypoallergenic
Ingredients
01 Low Molecular Collagen 02 Ceramide
03 Low Molecular Hyaluronic Acid 0044 Linoleic Acid
THANK YOU
